{
    "subject": "resource/Jean-Paul_Sartre",
    "predicate": "ontology/mainInterest",
    "object": "resource/Self-consciousness",
    "human_readable": "The main interest of Jean-Paul Sartre is Self-consciousness.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7633122205734253,
            "question": "What was Jean-Paul Sartre's primary area of interest?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7490214705467224,
            "question": "What was the main focus of Jean-Paul Sartre's intellectual pursuits?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6788892149925232,
            "question": "Which subject did Jean-Paul Sartre explore extensively?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6432550549507141,
            "question": "What aspect of human existence was most important to Jean-Paul Sartre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5085028409957886,
            "question": "What did Jean-Paul Sartre consider the most fundamental element of human experience?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48656293749809265,
            "question": "What concept did Jean-Paul Sartre focus on in his work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4757535755634308,
            "question": "What philosophical idea is central to Jean-Paul Sartre's writings?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4571710228919983,
            "question": "Jean-Paul Sartre's philosophical investigations centered around which idea?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4544079005718231,
            "question": "Jean-Paul Sartre's work primarily revolves around which theme?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43809425830841064,
            "question": "What key concept did Jean-Paul Sartre seek to understand through his philosophy?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The main interest of Jean-Paul Sartre is Self-consciousness.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7383_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jean-Paul Sartre's work primarily revolves around which theme?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7383_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jean-Paul Sartre's philosophical investigations centered around which idea?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7383_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What philosophical idea is central to Jean-Paul Sartre's writings?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7383_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7383_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7383_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7383_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7383_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7383_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7383_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7383_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7383_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7383_91.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7383_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format with the answer to your question:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that, according to the provided text, Sartre's work does indeed accentuate the intricate interconnectedness among consciousness, the external world, and self-awareness. Additionally, it discusses in detail his views on pre-reflective consciousness, reflective consciousness, and being-for-others, which are all related to self-consciousness. Therefore, the main interest of Jean-Paul Sartre is indeed Self-consciousness."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"The main interest of Jean-Paul Sartre is self-consciousness.\" The texts discuss Sartre's exploration and analysis of different levels of consciousness, including pre-reflective consciousness, reflective consciousness, and being-for-others. This indicates that self-consciousness plays a central role in Sartre\u2019s philosophical works, thus supporting the given statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}